--==本影片由 CMCT 团队 荣誉出品==--
更多精彩影视 请访问 http://cmct.cc
影片压制:木子鱼  字幕调校:木子鱼  招募Q号:76846146
救命呀
Please.
他跑到河边就算赢了
If he makes it to the river, he's won.
罗先生 不容许有漏网之鱼
We cannot allow that to happen, Mr. lopaki.
不要太靠近!
You're firing too close!
喝点白兰地?
Brandy?
杀人会上瘾是吗?
It's like a drug, isn't it?
就像吸毒一样
To bring a man down.
花钱买刺激值得吗?
Was it worth it?
值回票价 那就好
Every nickel. Good.
什么事?
Yes?
嗨 我要找道格·班德
Hi, I'm looking for Douglas Binder.
你是他的朋友?
You a friend of Mr. Binder's?
不是 我...
No, I...
我是他的女儿
I'm his daughter.
道格是好人 有礼貌
Doug was a nice man. He had manners.
他没说搬到那里去吗?
He didn't tell you where he was moving, did he?
他欠了些房租
He owed some rent, honey.
我叫他不要急 等他手头宽松再说
I told him he could wait to pay me till he got back on his feet.
他是否出了意外?
He wasn't in an accident, was he?
没有 他是被油具公司解雇
Oh no, he lost his job with the oil tool company.
他搬走的时候… 留下这个箱子
When Doug moved out, he left this box.
他说抵押在此  直到他偿清房租
He told me I could hold it till he could make up his back rent.
你知道他可能去哪吗?
Do you have any idea where he might be now?
你不妨到"女善人收容所"看看
You might try checking down in Our Lady of Charity.
原来是陆战队员
ELIJAH Marine, huh?
侦骑营的
Recon.
我也曾在那个单位
I was in the service for a while myself.
真的?
Really? Yeah.
你认识他吗?
Do you know him?
他偶而来这里
He comes here sometimes.
他是个好人
Nice guy, too.
若是遇到他 我会转告你在找他
If I see him, I'll tell him you're looking.
你知道他住在那里吗?
Do you happen to know where he lives?
恐怕你爸爸...
I'm afraid your daddy...
他跟我们一样  无家可归
Well, he was like the rest of us, out of doors.
你明白吗?
You know?
"半月餐厅"
"意外" 炖甘宝好吃吗?
How is that gumbo, Chance?
难以下咽
A tragedy.
不过咖啡勉强可以入口
The coffee was tolerable, though.
那也是要钱的
It ain't free, neither.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
又忘了带皮夹出来吗?
Leave your wallet in your tuxedo?
这一招我用过吗?
I play that one on you before?
是呀 吃甘宝的时候
Yeah. For the gumbo.
不错
That's right.
嘿 有硬币吗?
Hi. Do you have any change?
谢谢你
Thank you.
嗨 玛丽
Hi, Marie.
我父亲有回来拿信件吗?
Yes, I was wondering if my father came to pick up his mail yet.
他没有吗? 不用 谢谢 再见!
He hasn't? No, that's fine. Thank you. Bye-bye.
嘿 小美人
Hello, pretty lady.
别烦我
Leave me the hell alone.
这个给我们
We'll take the wallet.
再陪我玩玩如何?
How about a little extra, honey?
你们玩得开心吗?
You having fun?
小子 你自求多福吧!
Why don't you do yourself a favor, boy?
要求福的是你们
I think the favor is gonna be done for you.
不要怕
it's okay.
我叫你滚开!
I said, get lost!
带着你的狗党给我滚
Now, take your pig stick and your boyfriend
去搭巴士滚远一点
and find a bus to catch.
这个家伙很滑稽
Oh, this guy's funny.
来呀  放马过来!
Come on. Let's go!
来吧!
Let's go!
出招!
Come on!
真可惜 这地区本来太平
You know, it's a shame. This used to be such a nice part of town.
下次当心 钱财不要露白
Next time be more careful when you show your wallet.
没有警察 全市停摆!
Without cops, the city stops!
没有警察! 全市停摆!
Without cops, the city stops! Without cops, the city stops!
来 快点! 快来
Come on, let's hurry now! Come on.
警察罢工提早结束吗?
Will the strike end soon? Here you go.
"纽奥良市警察第三分局"
祝我生日快乐
Happy birthday to me.
对不起
Excuse me.
有何贵干?
Can I help you?
是 我要报人口失踪
Yeah, I need to fill out a missing person report.
我已经上了两班
Look, I just pulled a double shift.
明天好吗?
Why don't you catch me tomorrow.
好吧 现在办理
Okay. Why don't you catch me now.
失踪人姓名?
What is the name of the missing individual?
道格·班德
Douglas Charles Binder.
与报案人的关系?
Relationship of reporting party?
父女
Daughter.
有相片吗?
Okay. You got a picture? Mmm-hmm.
有最近的相片吗?
Got something a little more recent?
没有
No, I don't.
我父母已离异廿年了
See, my parents were divorced 20 years ago.
他有住址吗?
You got an address?
我猜想他是无家可归
I think my father was homeless.
我是来这里以后才知道
I didn't even know myself until I just came down here.
我搞不懂你要我做什么
Look, I'm not sure what you want me to do here.
我要你受理我报案
I want you to take my report.
通常失踪人口的认定
Well, generally, in order to be considered missing,
必须是有家不归者
you need somewhere to be missing from.
好吧
Fine.
捕快大人 既然你太忙了
Look, if you're too busy to do your job, Detective,
我去找不忙的人
then I'll find somebody who isn't so busy.
听我说...
Look...
你要找爸爸吗? 我劝你去教会打听
You want to find your father, take my advice, canvass the missions,
去问收容所
ask at the shelters,
不过要找个地头熟的人带路
but get somebody who knows the city to show you around,
否则我得受理你的失踪了
or I'll be filling out one of these on you.
喂 不用谢我
Hey, you're welcome.
注意 安静地听
All right, pipe down and listen up.
今早有12个缺 AB级或以上的水手
We got 12 positions this morning, Able Seaman or better.
叫到名字的到办公室去
When I call your name, come into the office, show your papers,
出示证件就可以上船
and you'll get your ship.
点名了 鲁易吉康巴斯 AB级水手
Here we go. First man, Gombas, Luigi. Able Seaman.
有
Right here.
史蒂文华德 二管轮
Walker, Steven. Second Engineer.
餐厅的人 说你可能会在这里
They told me at the cafe that you might be down here.
我有事找你商量
I need to talk to you about something.
我想时候不对
I don't think this is a good time now.
- 沃尔特  尼古斯 AB级水手  - 到
- Walters, Nichols D. Able Seaman. - Yeah.
要不要帮我做事?
How'd you like to work for me?
每天付你一百元
I'll pay you $100 a day.
做什么?
For doing what?
日薪百元在乎做什么吗?
For$100, does it really matter?
当然在乎
Actually, it does. Yeah.
做什么有关系
It does.
我要你帮我找一个人
Look, I really need you to help me find someone.
毕亚尔 伙夫
Gill, Bill. Cook.
你地头熟 显然也有本事自卫
You know this city, you obviously can take care of yourself.
"包意外" AB级水手
Boudreaux, C. Able Seaman.
亲爱的 我愿意帮助你
I would like to help you, darling.
可惜我要出差了
Looks like I'm gonna be out of town.
要出远门
Way out of town.
抱歉
Sorry.
"意外"我以为 你因为殴打船长被炒了
Chance. Thought you got blackballed about that thing with Captain McDonald.
那是天大的误会
That was a big misunderstanding, you know.
误会
Right.
听说打裂了下巴骨
Broke his damn jaw is what I heard.
你一定要代我问候船长
You make sure I said a big "hello."
慢着
Wait a minute.
强生说我可以复职
Johnson says I was reinstated.
公司准了 工会还不准
With the company. Not with the union.
你欠缴会费 老弟
You owe some dues here, boy.
一共217元
217 bucks.
这趟回来我会补缴
I'll pay that off on this cruise.
你明知欠会费不能出海
No. Nobody ships out if they're in arrears, you know that.
我没事做哪来的钱缴会费?
How am I gonna pay my dues if I can't get the job?
伙计 规定不是我订的
I don't make the rules, mate.
你上的那条船周末才起航
Look, your ride doesn't sail till the end of the week.
我若是弄到钱呢?
If I can get the money, then what?
我就让你出海
Then I'll let you ship out.
我会弄到钱
I'll get the money.
继续前进 拿回去
Keep going. Take it back.
你要找的人是欠你钱吗?
So, this guy you're looking for, he owes you money or something?
是我爸爸
He's my father.
好 我改变心意了
Okay, I changed my mind.
我帮你找两天 给我217元
I'll help you for two days, you'll pay me $217.
一言为定
It's a deal.
你来开车
You can drive.
我没有驾照 小姐
I don't have a driver's license, ma'am
你叫什么名字?
So, what's your name?
包意外 你呢?
Chance Boudreaux. What's your name?
叫娜特
It's Nat.
娜特?
Nat?
你父母给你起昆虫的名字
Your parents name you for a bug?
不是 是娜达莎的简称
No, actually, it's short for Natasha.
娜达莎
Natasha.
"意外"这算什么名字?
What kind of a name is Chance?
我妈是"意外"的怀了我
Well, my mama took one.
你怎么和父亲失散的?
So, how did you lose your papa?
我七岁时父母离婚...
My parents, they got divorced when I was seven and my father...
我父亲搬了出去
Well, he moved away.
我们开始通信 他还打电话来
We started to write and he even called me a couple of times.
三周前书信中断了
Three weeks ago the letters just stopped.
我有个朋友在此他能帮忙
I've got a friend here who can help us.
你看看排队的人 我到里面看看
You check the line, I'll look around inside.
有辣椒酱吗?
Hey, you don't have a bottle of hot sauce on ya, do ya?
艾利亚 你好吗?
Elijah. What's happening?
星期三供应碎肉烤饼
Wednesday meat loaf.
他们说是碎肉烤饼
I mean, they said it was meat loaf.
我以为你上船了
I thought you were gonna get a ship.
我的许可证丢了
I lost my boarding pass.
我有东西给你看
I've got something to show you.
原来你们认识
You two know each other?
昨天见过
We met yesterday.
见到我父亲没有?
Have you seen my father?
我见到次要的东西
I saw the next best thing.
昨天我在意大利广场  见到推车上有个睡袋
I was at Plaza D'ltalia yesterday, and I saw this sleeping bag in a cart.
上面有虎纹迷彩 属陆战队专有
It was a tiger stripe, like the kind they used to issue to recon guys.
你爸爸正好有一个
Your daddy had one just like it.
谢了 查理
Thanks, Charlie. You bet.
"D.班德"
"道格·班德"
"最热情的性爱电话"
别怪他 为了赚钱发传单
Don't be offended. He passed them out for money.
是呀 我也发传单
Yeah, I've had to do it myself.
到巴勒克街分发
Here. Barracks Street.
老爹 街两边都要发 下一个! 快!
Both sides this time, Grandpa. Next! Get!
"直接广告服务"
Here. Decatur. Lower half.
那不是我的好朋友"包意外"吗?
Well, if it ain't my good friend Boudreaux.
我以为你上船了
I thought you was gonna catch a ship.
也许我要留下来竞选市长
Maybe I'll stick around to run for mayor.
我们要找帮你做事的
We're looking for someone who worked for you.
他叫道格·班德
The man's name is Douglas Binder.
我不认识他
I never heard of him.
他却认识你
I think he knew you.
他帮你做过事吗?
Did he work for you, sir?
也许有 也许没有
Maybe he did, maybe he didn't.
记名字我的脑袋不行
I'm not too good with names.
我有相片
I have a photograph.
卜先生是说记容貌他也不行
What Mr. Poe is trying to say is he's not too good with faces.
是吗?
Right?
伦多 你好! 我不知道你有客人
Hello, Randal. I didn't know you had company.
我们正要走
We were just leaving.
应该回去找他
You know, we should go back up there.
现在不要 不要一道去
Not now. Not together.
姓卜的显然知道 我父亲的事
Poe knows something about my father, obviously.
你不去找他 我去
Look, if you don't want to go back up there, I'll just go back myself.
你若想找到你爸 要用心机
Hey. If you want to find your daddy, you're gonna have to work smarter,
不是蛮干
not harder.
娜达莎班德? 什么事?
Natasha Binder? What's the problem?
我有个噩耗
Miss Binder, I'm afraid I have some bad news.
我们找到你父亲的尸体
They found your father's body.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
法医验明正身了 怎么死的?
They made a positive I.D. How did it happen?
昨夜有一起火灾 第九区一楝废屋失火
There was a fire last night in an abandoned building in the Ninth Ward.
消防员在屋里找到尸体
The fire department discovered your father's body in one of the rooms.
我要去认他
I need to see him.
你爸爸被烧焦了
Your daddy was burned pretty badly.
辨认身份全靠
The identification had to be made from
比对他的军中牙科病历
dental charts in your father's service record.
你来凑什么热闹?
What's your involvement here?
我在帮她找爸爸
I was helping her find her daddy.
醒醒  你这只肥猪!
Wakey, wakey, you fat fuck!
福寿先生 你来有何贵干?
Oh, God! Mr. Fouchon, what are you doing here?
伦多 少废话 听着
Don't talk, Randal. Listen.
你放心
Don't worry about Randal.
他的耳朵很尖
He's all ears.
你没向万克立先生报告
When Mr. Van Cleaf came upon your visitors yesterday,
昨天有人来打听自愿玩游戏者
you neglected to tell him that they were inquiring about one of our volunteers.
福寿先生 那没什么
That was nothing, Mr. Fouchon.
这事非同小可 伦多
Oh, it was something, Randal.
上星期我们所猎杀的人
This man we hunted last night.
说出他的真实姓名
Why don't you tell us his real name?
你浑蛋
You fuck.
班德 道格·班德
Binder. Binder. Douglas Binder.
他不是我们挑选的人 是吗?
That is not the one we selected, is it?
我找不到你们要的人
I couldn't get the guy you asked for.
你要退伍军人 我就叫班德去
Look, you said you wanted a combat veteran, so I sent you Binder.
他得过更多的勋章
He has more medals.
他有家属
He had a family.
他们在打听了
Now they're asking questions.
饶了我吧 我赔不是了
Please. Please. I said I was sorry. I said...
我已经赔不是了
I said I was sorry.
你就是大意
Careless is what you are, Randal.
大意加愚蠢 再加一项赔不是
Careless and stupid, and now you're sorry, too.
他说他是一个人
He said he was alone.
我不知他有家属 真的!
I didn't know he had any relatives, honest.
你犯了错
You made a mistake?
是不是这个意思?
Is that what you're saying? Yeah.
你要弥补过失
And I see you're anxious to make up for it, aren't you?
是的 是 先生
Right. Yes, sir.
我们有新客户 他要挑选一个新"玩伴"
We've got another client and he's about to select a new playmate.
下一次派我们所要的人来
Next time, send us the one we ask for.
一定会 福寿先生 我发誓
I will, Mr. Fouchon, I swear.
我们彼此都了解了
I think we understand each other.
是吗? 不是?
Yes? No? Yes.
是
Yeah.
伦多
Randal.
如果我再来
I come back here,
就要切"猪排"了
I cut me a steak.
你已尽人事了
You did your best.
没有 我来晚了
No, I came too late.
天啊 他全部家当是一车两推车
I mean, Jesus, he was living out of a shopping cart.
可恶 他怎么不告诉我呢?
God damn it. Why didn't he just tell me?
怎么不向我求助呢?
Why didn't he ask for my help?
我也曾流落街头
I've been there myself on the street.
很难开口
It's hard.
很难伸手乞讨
It's hard to put your hand out.
我在想 如果我能
I just kept thinking if I could
对他说我爱他该多好
just tell him that I loved him.
因为他太爱你了
And because he loved you so much,
所以不想拖累你
he didn't want to pull you into it.
我们的"朋友"包意外
Our friend, Mr. Boudreaux.
得过银星勋章
Silver Star.
陆战队侦骑营
Marine Force Recon.
退伍以后到商船上做事
He joined the Merchant Service after he got out.
他的船长走私鸦片烟
His captain was smuggling opium.
包意外发觉之后 把他丢下海
When Boudreaux found out, he threw the man overboard.
从此以后他就失业了
He's been looking for work ever since.
他显然不好惹 别小看了他
He's obviously not someone we should underestimate.
他在海湾沼泽被伯父养大
He was raised in the bayous by his uncle.
我认为他会是个来劲的猎物
I think Mr. Boudreaux would make a very interesting quarry.
"法医验尸报告"
也许我应该拜访他好吗?
Maybe I should pay him a visit.
不要! 不要!
No, no, no, no.
派两个弟兄去找他"聊聊"
Send a couple of lads down there to have a chat with him, would you?
好
Yeah.
"警方查封 不可越线"
中奖了
Bingo.
包意外 好言相劝  滚出道奇市!
Some friendly advice, Boudreaux. Get the fuck outta Dodge!
今天滚! 转告你的贱女人
Do it today! And tell that bitch girlfriend of yours
叫她朝北方踩油门跑路!
to point her titties north and step on the gas!
见到你总教人开心
It's always nice to see you.
在吸引暴力这方面 你真有天分
You seem to have a real talent, Mr. Boudreaux, for attracting violence.
这表示我是坏人吗?
Does that make me a bad person?
我因何被捕? 因为没有挨打的执照吗?
What did you arrest me for? Getting beat up without a license?
谢谢你通知我
Thank you for calling me.
天啊 你好狼狈
Oh, my God, you look awful.
你的话伤我的心
Darling, you hurt my feelings.
这就是罪名
What we have here is a charge sheet.
越过查封线 擅闯禁区
Willfully crossing a police barrier, that's considered criminal trespass.
这位警官好心提醒 我的罪状
Yes, that officer was nice enough to mention that to me.
你来干什么?
What were you doing at the house?
你在火场找到的名牌
The dog tag you find in that fire?
那都是两块一组
They always come in twos.
所以我到火场去找另一块
So I went back to that place to look for the other one.
你爸爸不是死于火灾
Your daddy, he didn't die in the fire.
他是被谋杀
He was murdered.
没有他杀的证据
There's no evidence of that.
现在有了
There is now.
名牌是被尖锐的硬物穿透的
That hole in that tag was made by something sharp and hard.
我愿意拿房租打赌 是戴在他身上被穿透的
And I'll bet my rent money it was made when Binder was still wearing it.
何必大费手脚杀一个流浪汉
Now, why would somebody go through all this trouble to kill a homeless man?
你相信了吗?
Do you believe us now?
这里办案的速度慢
Look, honey, the wheels turn slow around here.
非常慢 虽慢还是要办
Real slow. But they do turn.
我要下令重新验尸 有助于查案
I'll order a new autopsy. This'll help.
你应该看医生
You should see a doctor.
我憎恨医生
I hate them doctors.
可恶!
Shit!
什么事?
What?
现在没空
No time now.
你打过越战?
So, you in Nam?
是呀 很久的事了
Yeah, a long time ago.
凭你的经历
It seems to me a man with your obvious experience
应该赚到很多钱
should be pulling down a lot more money.
只填一张表 就付我一百元吗?
You're gonna pay me 100 bucks to fill out a form?
如果你有经验我付得更多
I'll pay you a lot more than that if you got the experience.
什么样的经验
What kind of experience?
不感兴趣吗?
Well, maybe you ain't interested.
我来填表
I'll fill out the application.
你有家属吗?
You got any family? Anybody to worry about you?
有人记挂着你吗? 亲友?
Fiends? Anything like that?
我举目无亲
No, I got nobody.
你存五十万元到 我们在开曼群岛的银行户头
You'll deposit $500,000 in our account in a bank in the Cayman Islands.
不可在传真或电话中提到 我们的约定
Do not refer to our agreement by telex or in conversations on the phone.
有向导和追踪高手供你差遣
You'll be provided with a guide, trackers
任你选用称手的武器
and the weapon of your choice.
我们负责处理尸首
Naturally, we'll dispose of the body
包你安然离开 并提供你不在场的铁证
and provide you with an out-of-town, air-tight alibi.
席南先生 你只消做瞄准射击
Don't worry, Mr. Zenan, all you have to do is point and shoot.
席南先生己经选好目标
Mr. Zenan has made his selection.
姓罗培的黑人 由特种部队下来的
A black man named Roper. Used to be in Special Forces.
好极了
Excellent.
我看你的选择没问题
I don't see any problem with your choice.
少数猎杀多数 这本来就是特权
It has always been the privilege of the few to hunt the many.
军人  警察  飞行员
Soldiers, policemen, fighter pilots.
帮政府杀人不犯法
Men who kill for the government do so with impunity.
我们给你这小老百姓
Now all we do is offer the same opportunity
同样的生杀大权
for private citizens such as yourself.
这些游戏对手都是自愿的吗?
These opponents, they're volunteers?
差不多
More or less.
政府的杀人专利
The same government that's made murder their sole preserve,
训练出我们要的目标
they train our targets.
我们只猎杀退伍军人
We pride ourselves on only hunting combat veterans,
受过训练的战士
men who have the necessary skills
猎杀起来更刺激 万一被警方查获怎么办?
to make our hunts more interesting. What about the police?
我确信如果找到了 一定很刺激
I'm sure that they would be interested if they were to find out.
这位莫顿医师 在验尸报告上为我们护航
Dr. Morton here assists us with the formality of police autopsies.
我们来纽奥良并非碰巧
It's no accident that we're in New Orleans.
去年我们在巴西里约猎杀
Last year we conducted hunts in Rio de Janeiro at Carnival,
最近在南斯拉夫也办过 是呀
Yugoslavia during the late unpleasantness. Oh, yeah.
地球上总是有动乱的角落
You see, there's always some unhappy little corner of the planet
让我们做这种生意
where we can ply our trade.
好 福寿先生
All right, Mr. Fouchon.
我光顾你的生意
You have a client.
席南先生 谢谢光临
Well, thank you for visiting, Mr. Zenan.
莫医师会送你出去
Dr. Morton will show you to the oar.
我的银行会拨款
My bank will arrange the transfer of funds within the hour.
好极了
Excellent.
几时行动?
When do we go out?
安排好了我们会通知你
We'll contact you when the necessary arrangements have been made.
"全身按摩服务"
"阿拉伯脚踩式妙爽按摩"
意外 你来干什么?
Chance. What you doing here?
有秘密任务
Secret mission.
宝贝 揉我
Rub me, baby. Come on.
好呀 宝贝
Oh, yeah, baby.
老卜 你好
Hello, Poe.
搞什么鬼?
What the fuck?
想念我吗? 天啊 不要再整我了
You miss me? Christ, not again.
你少了一只耳朵 所以最好是听仔细
Looks like you're short an ear, so you better listen very carefully.
你有没有专心听?
Now, are you paying attention?
是谁派爪牙偷袭我?
Who sent those apes after me?
我不懂你的话
I don't know what you're talking about.
本市有两百万人
Two million people in this city.
少了个卜胖子谁会在乎? 万克立!
Who's gonna miss a fat slob like you, Poe? Van Cleef!
他叫万克立
His name was Van Cleef.
乖孩子 他在哪里?
Good boy. Where is he?
我不知他住在哪! 他不是美国人!
I don't know where he lives! He ain't even American!
我若不听话他会杀我 真的!
Look, he'll kill me if I don't do what he says!
去告诉你的男朋友万克立
Tell your boyfriend, Van Cleaf,
我会找到杀班德的人
I'm gonna find out who killed Douglas Binder.
你要是听懂了就哼一声
If you understand me, just grunt.
再哼一声
Again.
你收到我的便条没有?
Did you get my memo?
道格·班德
Binder, Douglas C.
我要你重新验尸
I want you to take another look at the post-mortem.
这张便条所列的罪证 会使班德成为他杀
That memo contains evidence that might make Binder's death a homicide.
你可以重验也可以不理
Now, you can act on it, Doctor, or you can file it,
若有必要由法院下传票提验
but if I have to get a court order for a formal inquest,
我会申请
I will.
你应该看看咳嗽的毛病
You should do something about that cough.
你从来不敲门吗?
Don't you ever knock?
我们有麻烦了 大麻烦
We have a problem. A big problem.
他们要我为班德重新验尸
They want me to redo the autopsy on Binder.
是谁要求的?
Who is it that's asking?
姓米契的警探
A detective named Mitchell.
班德的家属逼她重验
Binder's family's breathing down her neck.
可以收买她吗? 不能
Can we buy her? No.
我想我们已经不受欢迎了
I guess we've overstayed our welcome.
今夜是在纽奥良的最后猎杀
Tonight is our last hunt in New Orleans.
开门
Open it.
好滑稽的小人
What a funny little man.
我们得换风景了 去温带地方
A change of scenery's what we need. Something less tropical.
有丘陆重叠 有城堡
Rolling hills, castles.
东欧 可以"玩"好几年
Eastern Europe. We can work there for years.
老卜呢?
Where's Poe?
卜先生不能来
Mr. Poe couldn't make it.
他耳朵发炎了
He's got an ear infection.
他说有事要我做
Look, he said he'd have some work for me.
这个仍有可能
That may still be a possibility.
我们想请你玩一场游戏
We got a little game we'd like you to play with us.
这条藏钱腰带里面有一万元
This money belt has $10,000 in it.
你想要就给你 一文不少
It's all yours if you want it, every penny.
要我做什么?
What do I have to do?
规则很简单
The rules of the game are very simple.
只要你跑到河边 穿过市区十里路
All you have to do is get to the river. Ten miles through the city.
你能到河边 你就有一万元了
You and the money belt make it to the river, you're $10,000 richer.
放狗屁
Bullshit.
你想做受施舍的可怜虫吗
Maybe you like being the object of pity,
沿街乞讨 睡在雨中
begging for quarters, sleeping in the rain,
为了一碗汤听一小时的传道
listening to half an hour of fire and brimstone for a bowl of soup.
去你的
Man, fuck you.
今夜你就能改变一切
You could change everything tonight.
试想一万元能买多少东西
Think of what $10,000 could buy you.
可以买新衣 整理仪容
You could get new clothes, clean yourself up,
也敢正眼看人了
look men in the eyes when you pass them on the street.
这笔钱能使你再当大丈夫 而不是只能回忆当年之勇
This money could make you a man again, instead of the shadow of your former self.
我跑到河边就得到这笔钱
I get to the river, I get the cash.
一文不少
Every nickel.
假如到不了呢?
And if I don't make it?
罗培 你懂体育规则
You're a sports fan, Roper.
自己推想吧
Figure it out.
让你先跑五分钟 不要耽误
You've got a five minute head start. Don't waste it.
这是纽奥良 席南先生 不是贝鲁特
This is New Orleans, Mr. Zenan, not Beirut.
先生 你先
After you, sir.
席南先生 开枪机保险
Mr. Zenan, take it off "safe."
把他了结
Finish him.
我不要动手  他受伤了
I don't want him. He's wounded.
干掉他  不要 打中就好了
Finish him. I can't do that. I hit him.
我打中他了 走!
I shot him. Let go. Hey!
不要让我在猎犬面前丢脸
Listen, don't make me look bad in front of my dogs.
你自知为何而来
You know why you're here?
你付五十万元给我们 是想知道自己有没有活力
You paid us half a million dollars to find out if you're alive or dead.
现在了结他
Now finish him.
干掉他!
Finish him!
天啊 他为何不下手?
God, why didn't he go fishing?
现在你明白 为何要先付钱了吧
Now you understand why we insist on payment up front.
放狗去追杀他好吗?
Set the dogs on him, won't you, Pik?
我不要整夜追赶
I don't wanna be out here all night.
救我! 求求你!
Help me! Please!
救我!
Help me!
拜托! 救我!
Please! Help me!
走开 去找事做! 求求你!
Go on, get a job! Please!
求求你! 注意点! 该死! 你给我小心点
Please! Watch it! Damn! Watch yourself.
救我  救我!
Help me. Help me!
求求你 救命
Help me. Please.
救我呀 兄弟! 救我!
Hey, look! Come on, man!
报警呀 兄弟!
Hey, just call the police here or something!
想办法救我!
Help me!
鲁法 让我进去! 打烊了!
Come on. Let me in! No, we're closed!
让我进去!
Let me in!
伙计! 救我!
Hey, buddy! Come on!
走开  快走开!
Brother, get out of here. Come on, get out. Help me, man!
兄弟! 我没有零钱找!
Help me! I ain't got no change, man!
他曾经帮老卜发传单
He was passing out flyers for Randal Poe.
我们去拜访他
Let's pay him a visit.
伦多  伦多  伦多
Randal, Randal, Randal.
你要不辞而别吗?
You were gonna leave without saying goodbye?
我的老母生病了
My mama got sick in Biloxi.
我正要打电话给你
I was gonna call you, Mr. Van Cleaf.
你当然要 伦多
Of course you were, Randal.
你当然要
Of course you were.
我知道你不是有意伤我的心
I know you didn't mean to hurt my feelings.
看来我们错过好戏了
Looks like we missed the party.
伏身!
Get down!
趴着!
Stay down!
上  上  上!
Go, go, go!
我们走  我们不能丢下她!
Let's go. We can't just leave her here!
把他困住 缠住他
Keep him in the Quarter. Stay on his ass.
她死了 快走
She's dead. Come on.
掌龙头!
Grab the bar!
女士优先
Ladies first.
什么?
What?
毕竟是有最后一场猎杀
It appears we'll have one last hunt after all, Pik.
火车过去也许两小时半左右
The train went by maybe two, two and a half hours ago.
到了他的地盘上可能有危险
This could be dangerous. We're on his turf now.
谢谢你们能临时加入猎杀
Thank you, gentlemen, for making yourselves available on such snort notice.
我们在追一个厉害的猎物
We are stalking an exceptional opponent.
是世界级的高手
Truly a world-class trophy.
这一趟猎杀的价码
The price for participating in this little excursion
是每人七十五万元
is $750,000 each.
你们之中谁摇倒他
Should one of you be lucky enough to bring him down,
谁就享受免费
I'll consider that hunter's account paid in full.
要提防有鳄鱼吗?
Shouldn't we be worried about alligators or something?
为了使你放心 有鳄鱼
If it makes you feel better, yeah.
走 不要停
Come on, keep going.
到我大伯家还有很远的路
It's still a long way to Uncle Douvee's place.
至少他们找不到我们了
At least they won't be able to find us out here.
如果有大伯那样的追踪好手 就会追上来
Yes, they will, if they have a tracker as good as Uncle Douvee.
只要沿铁路就会追到
All they have to do is to check along the rail road.
我只有两三个小时
I'm just guessing we have a couple of hours.
也许更少 走  我们走
Maybe less. Come on. Let's go.
有没有小径什么的?
Isn't there a trail or something?
这就是小径
This is the trail.
你玩得很起劲是吗?
You're really enjoying yourself, aren't you, Chance?
我们若是累 他们也会累
If it's tough for us, it's tough for them.
你信得过我吗?
You trust me?
当然信得过
Of course I trust you.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
相信你到闭眼睛的程度吗?
Why do you want me to trust you with my eyes closed?
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
它死了吗? 没有死
Is it dead? Not hardly.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
给我的朋友们一个意外
I'm leaving a surprise for my friends.
龟儿子!
Son of a bitch!
我要折磨你然后吃掉你!
I'll fuck you, then I'll eat you!
如果你们安静点动作快点
If you would die quieter and pick up the pace,
包意外就没时闲安排意外
Boudreaux would have less time for these little surprises.
杰隆!
Jerome!
请你带路
Would you be so kind?
走路当心好吗? 我们走
And do watch your step, won't you? Let's go.
有时候我真佩服自己!
Sometime I amaze myself, me!
好酒能替猴子壮胆打老虎!
Good whiskey make jack rabbit slap the bear!
意外? 是啊!
Chance? Yeah!
意外!
Chance!
你是来看大伯吗?
You come to see your Uncle Douvee.
娜达莎 我大伯
Natasha, my Uncle Douvee.
我们来洗伤口包扎 不会痛
We'll fix him up good. Put bandage on it, no hurt.
孩子 要坚强!
Be strong, my boy.
有一伙人追杀我
Douvee, I've got some people after me.
我知道
I know.
我闻到味道了
I can smell them.
我给你的生日礼物 30-06口径在吗?
You've still got a . 30-06, the one I gave you for your birthday?
不在 被鳄鱼吞掉了
No. A gator ate it.
不过
But, uh,
你的散弹枪还在
I've still got your shotgun.
告诉我 这些人追杀你
So tell me, this man what chase after you,
是跟你有仇 还是为了好玩?
he mad at you for business or pleasure?
两者都有
Both.
我骑"爱维娜"到富奇湾
I'm going to take Elvira south, then to Bayou La Fouche,
储藏花车道具的地方
Mardi Gras graveyard.
你能叫它去就请便
If you can talk her into it, go ahead.
你要当心
You be careful.
别为我操心
Don't worry about me.
我喜欢热闹
I love the company.
当心 少了你变成我在猎杀他们
Be careful. Without you, I'm hunting them.
他不会有事的
He's gonna be all right.
来 我们走
Oui. Come. We go.
来 暍一口 不要弄洒了
Here, drink. But do not spill.
会把草烧焦
It kills the grass.
这里很干净 他们刚走!
The place is clean. He just left.
快卧倒!
Get the fuck down!
你们休想捉到我
等一下!
Hold it!
包意外才是我们的目标
Boudreaux is the target we're after.
你笨得像牛!
You are a fucking buffalo!
走!
Move!
包意外十五分钟前 往这边骑马走了
Boudreaux went this way, maybe 10, 15 minutes ago. He's on a horse.
他在引我们远离他的朋友
He's trying to lead us away from his friends.
快上车
Get in the fucking trucks.
走! 快走! 你快点好吗?
Move! Fucking move! Will you move? Move!
他们都是白痴
They're fucking brain-dead.
召直升机来 找包意外
Get the helicopter. Find Boudreaux.
我们在这边设埋伏
We'll set up an ambush this side of Bayou La Fouche.
我能从空中干掉他
I can take him from the air.
白痴也能
Any pinhead can take him from the air.
我要从地上了结他!
I wanna take him from the ground!
我能从空中干掉他
I can take him from the air.
要用行家手法
Be a professional, Pik.
你错了
You're making a mistake.
一定要把他逼到海湾地
Make sure he gets there, Pik.
是他
That's him.
喂 呆瓜!
Hey, pigeon.
阿福雷的杂货店在三公里外
Avril Pybus has a store two miles this way.
你去打电话报警
You go to a telephone, call the sheriff.
你知道… 你应该去报告警长
You know, chere, I think you should call the sheriff.
看来你的猎物愈来愈扎手
It appears your trophy is ripping us a new orifice.
我来给你们复习战略形势
Let me review the tactical situation for you, gentlemen.
包意外受了伤
Boudreaux is wounded.
他被赶到了无人烟之地
He's been pursued and harried across miles of open country.
他被困住了 以一敌廿
Now he's cornered and outnumbered 20 to 1.
他是一只讨人嫌的小虫
He's an annoying little fucking insect,
我要他被踩得扁扁地
and I want him stepped on, hard.
你没生我的气吧?
You're not angry with me, are you, Pik?
我不会生气
I don't get angry.
我只会杀人
I'm a professional.
我们上!
Let's move!
这情形不妙
This is not good.
如果现在走五小时可到墨西哥
If we walk away now, we can be in Mexico in five hours.
你怎么了?
What the fuck is the matter with you, Pik?
猎杀酒鬼把你软化了?
Hunting drunks in alleys made you soft?
这个龟儿子很厉害!
God, that son of a bitch is good!
可恶 我要轰掉他的脑袋
Goddamn it, I'm gonna blow his goddamn head off!
你们瞪什么眼?
What are you looking at, you sons of bitches?
你们为此花钱! 去杀他!
This is what you paid for! Get him!
封锁这地方
Seal off this place.
这龟儿子是我的
The son of a bitch is dying.
打烂了衬衫 抱歉
Sorry about the shirt.
稍安勿燥
Ah, give it a rest, pal.
现在怎么办?
Now what do you want to do?
现在
Now,
除了"意外"每人给他一箭
now we put arrow into everyone what's not Chance, huh?
来
Come.
你这臭贱人!
You fucking bitch!
你看你干的事
Now, now look what you do.
枪给我 我来解决这些坏人
Give me this gun. I take care of all these bad guys.
枪给我!
Give me this gun!
我叫你去求援
I told you to go for help.
我们支援你
But we help. We're here to help.
这么多人要杀你 我们来助阵
All these men try to kill you. We're here to help.
包意外 包意外 包意外
Boudreaux, Boudreaux, Boudreaux.
我到处找你
I've been looking all over for you.
你找错地方了
You've been looking in the wrong places.
那好呀
That's good,
因为我知道你不愿伤我的感情
'cause I know you wouldn't want to hurt my feelings.
你起得来吗?
Can you get up?
我不能跳舞但是起得来
I cannot dance, but I can get up.
你龟儿子走运!
You lucky son of a bitch!
你还想吃几枪?
You want some more of that?
被猎杀的滋味如何?
How does it feel to be hunted?
你告诉我呀!
You tell me!
你应该更了解
You should know better.
我在世界的每个地方 都从事交易
There isn't a country in the world I haven't fired a bullet in.
你杀不了我!
You can't kill me!
你杀不了我
You can't kill me.
我历经过各个战场
I'm on every battlefield.
是个神勇的战士!
There's no winner here!
我未见过
I don't see one.
你正在看着他!
You're looking at him!
来呀 龟儿子! 拿出你的绝招!
Come on, you son of a bitch! Take your best shot!
包意外!
Chance!
包意外
Chance.
孩子!
My boy!
只管射杀他!
Just shoot him!
你不会做的 你会吗?
You won't do that, will you Mr. Boudreaux?
包意外!
Chance!
拜托!
Please!
他若开枪会打死你
If he shoots me, he'll kill you.
你错不该用散弹枪
He's picked the wrong tool for the job.
把枪放下
Put the weapon down
否则我刺穿她!
or I'll run her through!
你看 班德小姐
You see, Miss Binder,
你要报父仇我能了解
you I can understand, it was a matter of family.
你跟那些流浪汉毫无瓜葛
You had nothing in common with those people.
为什么要插手跟我作对?
What made you want to complicate my life like this?
穷人也有无聊的时候
Poor people get bored, too.
- 来这里 - 不要!
- Come here. - No, please!
帮我装子弹
Load me.
狩猎季节结束了
Hunting season is over.
什么声音?
What is this noise?
我正梦到关于你的事
I was dreaming.
亲爱的 我想你
Chere, I think about you.
我跟火鸡说 你没把老鹰杀死
I tell this turkey, he no kill this eagle.
我的头好痛
Some headache I got here.
我的天
Oh, my God.
什么?
What?
我大概伤得很重
I think I hurt pretty bad.
这个祸可闯大了!
Now this, this real catastrophe!
糟糕透了
This real bad.
是糟糕透了
Yeah, real bad.